<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ScrollView xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:background="#000000">

    <LinearLayout
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:orientation="vertical">

        <LinearLayout
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:gravity="center_vertical"
            android:orientation="horizontal"
            android:paddingStart="16dp"
            android:paddingTop="16dp"
            android:paddingEnd="16dp"
            android:paddingBottom="16dp">

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/titleGuidelines"
                android:layout_width="0dp"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:layout_weight="1"
                android:text="Event Lottery"
                android:textColor="#FFFFFF"
                android:textSize="28sp"
                android:textStyle="bold" />

            <ImageButton
                android:id="@+id/guidelinesSettingsButton"
                android:layout_width="40dp"
                android:layout_height="40dp"
                android:background="@android:color/transparent"
                android:contentDescription="Settings"
                android:src="@android:drawable/ic_menu_manage"
                android:tint="#FFFFFF" />
        </LinearLayout>

        <View
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="1dp"
            android:background="#2A2A2A" />

        <TextView
            android:id="@+id/guidelinesBackButton"
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginStart="16dp"
            android:layout_marginTop="14dp"
            android:text="← Back to Home"
            android:textColor="#FFFFFF"
            android:textSize="18sp" />

        <TextView
            android:id="@+id/guidelinesText"
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginTop="18dp"
            android:paddingStart="16dp"
            android:paddingEnd="16dp"
            android:paddingBottom="16dp"
            android:textColor="#E6E6E6"
            android:textSize="15sp"
            android:lineSpacingExtra="4dp"
            android:text="1. Purpose of the App&#10;&#10;The Event Lottery System helps people register for popular community events in a fair way. Instead of spots being taken by whoever clicks first, users can join a waiting list and are selected randomly.&#10;&#10;This system gives everyone a fair chance to participate, even if they cannot register immediately when an event opens.&#10;&#10;2. General Rules&#10;&#10;To keep the platform fair and enjoyable for everyone, please follow these rules:&#10;&#10;- Each user may join the waiting list once per event.&#10;- Users should provide accurate personal information when registering.&#10;- If selected for an event, users must accept or decline the invitation within the given time.&#10;- If there is no response, the spot may be offered to another entrant.&#10;&#10;3. How the Lottery Works&#10;&#10;- Users join the waiting list during the event registration period.&#10;- When registration closes, the system randomly selects participants.&#10;- Selected users receive a notification inviting them to register.&#10;- If someone declines or does not respond, another person from the waiting list may be selected.&#10;- This process continues until all available spots are filled.&#10;&#10;4. Responsibilities of Entrants&#10;&#10;- Join waiting lists only for events they plan to attend.&#10;- Respond to invitations as soon as possible.&#10;- Follow any rules set by the event organizer.&#10;- Keep their profile information up to date.&#10;- Entrants can leave a waiting list at any time before the lottery draw.&#10;&#10;5. Responsibilities of Organizers&#10;&#10;- Provide clear and accurate event details (date, time, location, capacity).&#10;- Set registration start and end dates.&#10;- Use the lottery system fairly.&#10;- Communicate updates to entrants through the app.&#10;- Organizers may update or cancel events if necessary.&#10;&#10;6. QR Code Access&#10;&#10;Events may include a QR code to make registration easier. Scanning a QR code takes users directly to the event page where they can view details and join the waiting list. QR codes should only be used for legitimate event promotion.&#10;&#10;7. Location Verification&#10;&#10;Some events may require location verification. If enabled, the app may check device location when users join the waiting list. Location data is used only for this purpose.&#10;&#10;8. Notifications&#10;&#10;The app may send notifications when:&#10;- A user is selected for an event&#10;- A user is not selected&#10;- An event is updated or cancelled&#10;- Organizers send important announcements&#10;&#10;Users can choose to disable notifications in settings.&#10;&#10;9. Privacy and Data&#10;&#10;Personal information is stored securely using Firebase and only used for event registration and communication. Users can delete their profile at any time.&#10;&#10;10. Administrative Oversight&#10;&#10;Administrators help manage the platform by removing inappropriate events, removing abusive profiles, managing uploaded images, and reviewing notification logs.&#10;&#10;11. Fair Use&#10;&#10;Users who misuse the platform may be removed. Examples include creating multiple accounts to increase lottery chances, uploading inappropriate/offensive content, or violating platform guidelines." />

    </LinearLayout>

</ScrollView>
